desiplaza.tv 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Desiplaza TV - Face of the Community.

Desiplaza.TV Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on March 31st 2015.  
Company, Inc. (Desiplaza LLC) ("us", "we", or "our") operates [http://www.desiplaza.tv](http://www.desiplaza.tv./) This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.  
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

Information Collection And Use  
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").

**Any Information we collect from may be used in one of the following ways**.

* To improve your experiece (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
*To improve our website (We continuously strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
* To Process transactions, Your personal information either public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your concent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased products or service information, etc.,

*To send periodic Emails , The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, to send updateson Upcoming events & happenings, company news, updates, related products or service informations, etc.,

Note : If any time you would like to unsubscriber from receiving future emails, we include detailes unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

*To Administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site features.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

* We do not use cookies

*Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. this does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we beleive release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occationally at our discretion, we may include or offer 3rd party products or services on our website. These 3rd party sites have seperate and independant privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and archives of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy only**

This online privacy policy applies only to the information collected through the website and not to information collected offline.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding the privacy policy you may contact us using the Information below.

Desiplaza Studios  
1404 W Walnut Hill Ln, Suite 110  
Irving, Texas 75038

Email : [dallasidol2015@gmail.com](mailto:dallasidol2015@gmail.com)  
Facebook Twitter Google+ Share
